cleanpcguide.com 2012-10-03

# Privacy Policy | Cleanpcguide.com

Overview:  
Cleanpcguide.com recognizes that privacy is an important issue and we respect and protect the privacy of our users. Cleanpcguide.com does not distribute Individually Identifiable Information about our users to any third party without first receiving direct permission. “Individually Identifiable Information” is information that identifies a specific user such as your name, address or e-mail address.

This privacy policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use Cleanpcguide.com’s service and how we intend to use the information to help personalize your news reading experience while not disclosing Individually Identifiable Information except in accordance herewith.

Cookies:  
When you log on to Cleanpcguide.com for the first time, Inform sends a “cookie” to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. Cleanpcguide.com uses cookies to customize your news and serve you advertisements that are hopefully useful.

Data Collection:  
When you use Cleanpcguide.com, we track your activity with respect to the category and substance of articles read, sites visited, subject matter investigated and content forwarded to other persons, among other activities. Inform uses this data to perform statistical analyses and target news content and advertising specifically to each user. This means that users see advertising that is most likely to interest them. We only reveal information to our advertisers and other third parties in aggregate form or as otherwise permitted pursuant to this Privacy Policy. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

Displays & Links:  
The stories linked to by Cleanpcguide.com are developed completely independently from Cleanpcguide.com and by people over whom Cleanpcguide.com has no control. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data, or solicit personal information.

Consent:  
By using Cleanpcguide.com, you consent to the collection and use of your information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. Cleanpcguide.com may decide to change this policy from time to time. If we do, we will notify you on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, what we do with it and and with whom we share it.

Changes to this Policy:  
Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. Regardless, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice.
